Tuesday will be power plant day and bridge day all wrapped on in one in Iran.
There will be nothing like it.
Open the effing straight, you crazy bastards, or you'll be living in hell.
Just watch!
Praise be to Allah, President Donald J. Trump.
The straight is open, for the record.
The straight of Ormuz is open.
It's just not open to folks who are supporting the empire.
It's just not open for anybody aligned with the International Energy Agency,
the International Monetary Fund, and the World Bank,
who are all in cahoots.
They're all a cabal.
The straight is open, baby.
China got their oil.
Malaysia got their oil.
India got their oil.
The straight is open.
It's just not open for y'all.
Support a real one.